{
  "entities_found": [
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "of the Faucitt Family Trust\n2. Accountant for all RegimA companies\n3. Controller of financial systems\n4. Co"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "es instructed payments) - Chain of command\n- SF3: Strategic Logistics R5.4M stock adjustment - Fraud Bantjies had motiv"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Villa Via",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "Relevant Events\n\n**June 6, 2025:** Daniel exposes Villa Via fraud to Bantjies (unknowingly reporting to perpe"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "# SF1: Ketoni R18.75M debt to FFT (Bantjies conflict as George Group CFO)M)\n\n**Annexure Referenc"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "ments the substantial debt of R18.75M Ketoni debt to FFT (Bantjies conflict as George Group CFO) creates a c"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "bt:\n\n**Trust Records:**\n- Loan agreements between Bantjies and the Faucitt Family Trust\n- Trust financial sta"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies\n",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "es showing the debt\n- Aged debtor reports listing Bantjies\n- Interest calculations and accruals\n- Any corresp"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "- Original trust deed\n- Any amendments appointing Bantjies as trustee\n- Trustee acceptance documentation\n- Ma"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "- Peter's founding affidavit (showing omission of Bantjies as trustee)\n- Court application documents (showing"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "nature\n\n**Conflict Analysis:**\n- Timeline showing Bantjies certified affidavit while being undisclosed truste"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "hile being undisclosed trustee\n- Timeline showing Bantjies certified affidavit while owing R18.75M (Ketoni debt to FFT) to the tr"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "Interest Analysis\n\n### Triple Conflict Structure\n\nBantjies occupied three conflicting positions simultaneousl"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "very\n\nThe R18.75M (Ketoni debt to FFT) debt provides clear motive for Bantjies to:\n\n1. **Dismiss Daniel's audit request** (June 1"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "June 6, 2025:** Daniel exposes Villa Via fraud to Bantjies (unknowingly reporting to perpetrator)\n\n**June 10,"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "gly reporting to perpetrator)\n\n**June 10, 2025:** Bantjies dismisses Daniel's audit request (4 days after fra"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "l's audit request (4 days after fraud exposure)\n- Bantjies had R18.75M (Ketoni debt to FFT) reasons to prevent audit\n- Audit woul"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "nterests, not trust's interests\n\n**August 2025:** Bantjies certifies Peter's founding affidavit as Commission"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "ations\n\n### Breach of Fiduciary Duty\n\nAs trustee, Bantjies had duty to:\n- Disclose conflicts of interest\n- Ac"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": " personal benefit\n\nThe R18.75M (Ketoni debt to FFT) debt demonstrates Bantjies acted in personal interest, not trust's interest.\n"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": " Fraud Facilitation\n\nThe debt provides motive for Bantjies to:\n- Conceal fraud from beneficiaries\n- Dismiss l"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "ructure\n- SF4: SARS audit email (Rynette claiming Bantjies instructed payments) - Chain of command\n- SF3: Str"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "trategic Logistics R5.4M stock adjustment - Fraud Bantjies had motive to conceal\n\n**Related Narrative Section"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies\n",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "Events:**\n- June 6, 2025: Daniel exposes fraud to Bantjies\n- June 10, 2025: Bantjies dismisses audit request\n"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "Daniel exposes fraud to Bantjies\n- June 10, 2025: Bantjies dismisses audit request\n- August 2025: Bantjies ce"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": ": Bantjies dismisses audit request\n- August 2025: Bantjies certifies Peter's affidavit\n\n## Notes for Legal Te"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "s annexure demonstrates:\n\n1. **Clear motive** for Bantjies to prevent fraud discovery (R18.75M (Ketoni debt to FFT) debt)\n2. **Co"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "using pete@regima.com) - Control structure\n- SF4: SARS audit email (Rynette claiming Bantjies instructed"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Peter Faucitt",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "k of Access\n\nThe evidence should demonstrate that Peter Faucitt:\n\n**No Computer Access:**\nPeter does not use a co"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Rynette Farrar",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "ns screenshots and system logs demonstrating that Rynette Farrar controlled the Sage accounting system using Peter"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Rynette Farrar",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "e Sections:**\n- Part II: The Network of Control - Rynette Farrar: The Administrator\n- Part II: The Network of Cont"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "took instructions from Bantjies, not Peter\n- SF8: Linda employment records - Rynette's sister employed as"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "count had full administrative privileges over all RegimA company accounts.\n\n**Transaction Records:**\nScreen"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "dumping of two years of unallocated expenses into RegimA Worldwide.\n\n**Email Integration:**\nScreenshots sho"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "ommunications with banks, and correspondence with RegimA staff.\n\n**System Configuration:**\nScreenshots of e"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": " administrative access to Sage accounting for all RegimA companies, with ability to create, modify, and del"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": ":** Two years of unallocated expenses dumped into RegimA Worldwide\n- Transaction processed through Sage sys"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "were actually composed and sent by Rynette:\n\n**To RegimA Staff:**\nInstructions regarding accounting procedu"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Villa Via",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "aliatory action\n\n**June 6, 2025:** Daniel exposes Villa Via fraud to Bantjies\n- Fraud involved transactions p"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies\n",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "June 6, 2025:** Daniel exposes Villa Via fraud to Bantjies\n- Fraud involved transactions processed through Sa"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "directly supports SF4, where Rynette claimed that Bantjies instructed her to make substantial payments. This "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "f command:\n\n**Not Peter → Rynette**, but rather **Bantjies → Rynette**\n\nThis demonstrates that Rynette took i"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "'s email identity. The control structure was:\n\n1. Bantjies (undisclosed trustee and R18.75M (Ketoni debt to FFT) debtor) provided"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "trol over these assets, and the real controllers (Bantjies and Rynette) were the ones engaging in misconduct."
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "# Cross-References\n\n**Related Annexures:**\n- SF1: Bantjies debt documentation - Establishes who actually cont"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "e@regima.com identity\n4. **Chain of command** was Bantjies → Rynette, not Peter → Rynette\n5. **False affidavi"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "munications to regimaskin.co.za (owned by her son Adderory), all while using Peter's identity.\n\n**Shopify Sy"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "ually executed by Rynette.\n\n## Connection to SF4 (SARS Audit Email)\n\nThe SF2 evidence directly supports "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "blishes who actually controlled operations\n- SF4: SARS audit email - Confirms Rynette took instructions "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Shopify",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "riggered immediate retaliation\n\n**May 22, 2025:** Shopify audit trail becomes unavailable (7 days after con"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Shopify",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "n Adderory), all while using Peter's identity.\n\n**Shopify System Cancellations:**\nInstructions to cancel Sh"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Shopify",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "fy System Cancellations:**\nInstructions to cancel Shopify systems and automation tools, sent from pete@regi"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "supplied by Adderory (Rynette's son's company) to RegimA Skin Treatments, suggesting systematic fraud and t"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "son's company) supplied the same type of stock to RegimA Skin Treatments, including:\n- Purchase orders from"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "kin Treatments, including:\n- Purchase orders from RegimA to Adderory\n- Invoices from Adderory to RegimA\n- P"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA\n",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "om RegimA to Adderory\n- Invoices from Adderory to RegimA\n- Product specifications matching disappeared stoc"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "Logistics and stock being supplied by Adderory to RegimA Skin Treatments. Evidence of temporal proximity su"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "ppears in Adderory's inventory and is supplied to RegimA Skin Treatments, likely at marked-up prices.\n\n**St"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "eter made unauthorized transfers of R900,000 from RegimA SA on February 14-15, 2025, without Daniel's autho"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "rity as co-director.\n\n**R1,035,000 Unpaid Debt:**\nRegimA Skin Treatments owes R1,035,000 to Kayla's estate "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "s.\n\n**Customer Diversion:**\nRevenue diverted from RegimA operations to regimaskin.co.za (owned by Adderory)"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": " Strategic Logistics to Adderory and then sold to RegimA at marked-up prices, this constitutes transfer pri"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "# SF3: Strategic Logistics R5.4M Stock Adjustment\n\n**Annexure Reference:** S"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "*Subject:** R5.4 Million Stock \"Disappeared\" from Strategic Logistics  \n**Relevance:** Evidence of systematic fraud and"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "e disappearance of R5,400,000 worth of stock from Strategic Logistics (SLG), attributed to a \"stock adjustment\" indicat"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "stment Rates:**\nAnalysis of stock adjustments for Strategic Logistics over previous years, demonstrating that normal ad"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "justment in question).\n\n**Sales Volume Context:**\nStrategic Logistics sales figures showing that R5.4M represents 46% o"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "scription of the stock type that disappeared from Strategic Logistics, including product codes, descriptions, and speci"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": " the relationship between stock disappearing from Strategic Logistics and stock being supplied by Adderory to RegimA Sk"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "cing Analysis:**\nComparison of stock valuation in Strategic Logistics vs. pricing charged by Adderory to RegimA, potent"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "atic fraud scheme:\n\n**Step 1: Stock Acquisition**\nStrategic Logistics (controlled by Faucitt Family Trust) acquires sto"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "sical Transfer**\nStock is physically removed from Strategic Logistics warehouse without proper documentation or authori"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "d-up prices.\n\n**Step 4: Accounting Manipulation**\nStrategic Logistics writes off R5.4M as \"stock adjustment,\" creating "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "\n\n**Unknown Date:** R5.4M stock \"disappears\" from Strategic Logistics\n- Stock physically removed from warehouse\n- No pr"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "sfer Pricing Fraud\n\nIf stock was transferred from Strategic Logistics to Adderory and then sold to RegimA at marked-up "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "tain complete stock adjustment documentation from Strategic Logistics\n2. Obtain historical stock adjustment rates for c"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Villa Via",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "ette's false claim to Jacqui that it was paid.\n\n**Villa Via 86% Profit Margin:**\nVilla Via (trust-owned) char"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Villa Via",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "at it was paid.\n\n**Villa Via 86% Profit Margin:**\nVilla Via (trust-owned) charged 86% profit margin rent to g"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Villa Via",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": " discover fraud\n\n**June 6, 2025:** Daniel exposes Villa Via fraud to Bantjies\n- Daniel's analysis may have be"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Villa Via",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "y blocking audit\n- Four days after Daniel exposed Villa Via fraud\n\n## Legal Implications\n\n### Theft and Fraud"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": " the SARS audit email (SF4), Rynette claimed that Bantjies instructed her to make substantial payments. This "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "orized the Stock Adjustment?**\nIf Rynette claimed Bantjies instructed payments, did Bantjies also instruct or"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "Rynette claimed Bantjies instructed payments, did Bantjies also instruct or approve the R5.4M stock write-off"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "simply written off as \"stock adjustment\" suggests Bantjies knew about and approved the fraud.\n\n**Connection t"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "d expenses (dumped March 30, 2025) occurred while Bantjies was accountant and Rynette controlled the accounti"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "ystem\n- R5.4M written off as \"stock adjustment\"\n- Bantjies (as accountant) should have investigated but did n"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies\n",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "June 6, 2025:** Daniel exposes Villa Via fraud to Bantjies\n- Daniel's analysis may have been approaching disc"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": " have been approaching discovery of stock fraud\n- Bantjies had motive to prevent further investigation\n- Imme"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "mmediate retaliation followed\n\n**June 10, 2025:** Bantjies dismisses Daniel's audit request\n- Audit would hav"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "- Audit would have discovered R5.4M stock fraud\n- Bantjies protected fraud scheme by blocking audit\n- Four da"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "# Cross-References\n\n**Related Annexures:**\n- SF1: Bantjies debt documentation - Motive to conceal fraud (R18."
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "M debt)\n- SF4: SARS audit email - Rynette claimed Bantjies instructed payments\n- SF5: Adderory company regist"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies\n",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "ck fraud)\n- June 6, 2025: Daniel exposes fraud to Bantjies\n- June 10, 2025: Bantjies dismisses audit request\n"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "Daniel exposes fraud to Bantjies\n- June 10, 2025: Bantjies dismisses audit request\n\n## Notes for Legal Team\n\n"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "** Evidence of systematic fraud and connection to Adderory stock supply\n\n## Executive Summary\n\nThis annexure"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "ment rate. The same type of stock was supplied by Adderory (Rynette's son's company) to RegimA Skin Treatmen"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "ative of fraud rather than operational loss.\n\n### Adderory Connection Evidence\n\n**Stock Type Identification:"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "oduct codes, descriptions, and specifications.\n\n**Adderory Supply Records:**\nDocumentation showing Adderory "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "*Adderory Supply Records:**\nDocumentation showing Adderory (Rynette's son's company) supplied the same type "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "ents, including:\n- Purchase orders from RegimA to Adderory\n- Invoices from Adderory to RegimA\n- Product spec"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "se orders from RegimA to Adderory\n- Invoices from Adderory to RegimA\n- Product specifications matching disap"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "m Strategic Logistics and stock being supplied by Adderory to RegimA Skin Treatments. Evidence of temporal p"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "ion in Strategic Logistics vs. pricing charged by Adderory to RegimA, potentially revealing markup and trans"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "orization, creating a \"disappearance.\"\n\n**Step 3: Adderory Supply**\nThe same type of stock appears in Addero"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "derory Supply**\nThe same type of stock appears in Adderory's inventory and is supplied to RegimA Skin Treatm"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "ating a loss in the trust-controlled entity while Adderory (Rynette's son's company) generates profit from s"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "m RegimA operations to regimaskin.co.za (owned by Adderory), following domain registration on May 29, 2025.\n"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "on of removal\n- Same stock type later supplied by Adderory\n\n**Unknown Date:** Stock adjustment processed in "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "mbined with the same stock type being supplied by Adderory, constitutes prima facie evidence of theft and fr"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "stock was transferred from Strategic Logistics to Adderory and then sold to RegimA at marked-up prices, this"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "nette claimed Bantjies instructed payments\n- SF5: Adderory company registration and stock supply - Same stoc"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "on and stock supply - Same stock type supplied by Adderory\n\n**Related Narrative Sections:**\n- Part II: The N"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "e Sections:**\n- Part II: The Network of Control - Adderory (Rynette's Son): The Beneficiary\n- Part III: Sect"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "involving R5.4M stock transfer\n2. **Connection to Adderory** (Rynette's son's company) through same stock ty"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "l stock adjustment rates for comparison\n3. Obtain Adderory supply documentation showing same stock type\n4. P"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "are timeline correlating stock disappearance with Adderory supply\n5. Obtain SARS audit documentation referen"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "to Bantjies, Rynette, and her family members.\n\n## SARS Audit Context (Connection to SF4)\n\nThe R5.4M stoc"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "stock adjustment was among the amounts subject to SARS audit. In the SARS audit email (SF4), Rynette cla"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "s among the amounts subject to SARS audit. In the SARS audit email (SF4), Rynette claimed that Bantjies "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": " - Motive to conceal fraud (R18.75M (Ketoni debt to FFT) debt)\n- SF4: SARS audit email - Rynette claimed Bantjies instructed"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "tock disappearance with Adderory supply\n5. Obtain SARS audit documentation referencing the stock adjustm"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Peter Faucitt",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "mal Structure (as represented in affidavits):**\n- Peter Faucitt: Founder and Main Trustee\n- Rynette Farrar: Bookk"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Rynette Farrar",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "RS (South African Revenue Service) audit in which Rynette Farrar claimed that Bantjies instructed her to make subs"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Rynette Farrar",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "s):**\n- Peter Faucitt: Founder and Main Trustee\n- Rynette Farrar: Bookkeeper/Administrator\n- Expected chain: Peter"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Rynette Farrar",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "ndisclosed trustee, accountant, R18.75M (Ketoni debt to FFT) debtor\n- Rynette Farrar: Administrator taking instructions from Bantjies\n"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Rynette Farrar",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "e Hidden Hand\n- Part II: The Network of Control - Rynette Farrar: The Administrator\n- Part II: The Network of Cont"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "ossible subject of Bantjies's instructions\n- SF8: Linda employment records - Sister employed in same cont"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "wo years of unallocated expenses were dumped into RegimA Worldwide with a 12-hour deadline. The SARS audit "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "dge or involvement in actual operations\n\n### SF3: Strategic Logistics Stock Adjustment\n\nIf Bantjies instructed substant"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "nism for executing Bantjies's instructions\n- SF3: Strategic Logistics stock adjustment - Possible subject of Bantjies's"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Villa Via",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "une 6, 2025: Daniel Exposes Fraud\n\nDaniel exposed Villa Via fraud to Bantjies. If Daniel's analysis was also "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "# SF4: SARS Audit Email (Rynette Claiming Bantjies Instructed Payments)\n\n**Annexure Reference:** SF4 "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "Subject:** Email Evidence Showing Rynette Claimed Bantjies Instructed Substantial Payments  \n**Relevance:** R"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": " \n**Relevance:** Reveals actual chain of command (Bantjies → Rynette, not Peter → Rynette)\n\n## Executive Summ"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "rvice) audit in which Rynette Farrar claimed that Bantjies instructed her to make substantial payments. This "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "emonstrating that the actual chain of command was Bantjies → Rynette, not Peter → Rynette as implied in Peter"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "email reveals that Rynette took instructions from Bantjies (the undisclosed trustee and R18.75M (Ketoni debt to FFT) debtor) rath"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "plete email from Rynette in which she states that Bantjies instructed her to make substantial payments. The e"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": " whether SARS accepted Rynette's explanation that Bantjies instructed the payments.\n\n### Chain of Command Evi"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "on Documentation:**\nAny written instructions from Bantjies to Rynette regarding payments, accounting entries,"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies\n",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "te Farrar: Administrator taking instructions from Bantjies\n- Actual chain: Bantjies → Rynette\n- Peter: Figure"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "taking instructions from Bantjies\n- Actual chain: Bantjies → Rynette\n- Peter: Figurehead with no actual contr"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "ons of Rynette's Statement\n\nRynette's claim that \"Bantjies instructed me to make the payments\" reveals severa"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": " the payments\" reveals several critical facts:\n\n**Bantjies Gave Instructions:**\nBantjies, not Peter, was dire"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "r financial management.\n\n**Bantjies's Conflict:**\nBantjies was instructing payments while owing R18.75M (Ketoni debt to FFT) to t"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "rests.\n\n## Connection to Other Evidence\n\n### SF1: Bantjies Debt Documentation\n\nThe SARS audit email takes on "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "mbined with evidence of Bantjies's R18.75M (Ketoni debt to FFT) debt. Bantjies was instructing substantial payments while being a"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "structured to benefit Bantjies's interests?\n- Did Bantjies use control over payments to protect his position?"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "### SF3: Strategic Logistics Stock Adjustment\n\nIf Bantjies instructed substantial payments (per SARS email), "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "ructed substantial payments (per SARS email), did Bantjies also instruct or approve the R5.4M stock adjustmen"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": " Rynette's Defense Strategy\n\nRynette's claim that Bantjies instructed the payments appears to be a defense st"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "jies:**\nRynette admitted taking instructions from Bantjies rather than the nominal trustee (Peter).\n\n**Questi"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": " trustee (Peter).\n\n**Question of Authority:**\nDid Bantjies have authority to instruct payments? If he was und"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "y established.\n\n**Conflict of Interest:**\nEven if Bantjies had authority, his R18.75M (Ketoni debt to FFT) debt created conflict "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "explaining why expenses were unallocated (because Bantjies instructed payments without proper documentation)."
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "t email, this would provide additional motive for Bantjies to retaliate against Daniel.\n\n### June 10, 2025: B"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": " to retaliate against Daniel.\n\n### June 10, 2025: Bantjies Dismisses Audit\n\nBantjies dismissed Daniel's audit"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "el.\n\n### June 10, 2025: Bantjies Dismisses Audit\n\nBantjies dismissed Daniel's audit request four days after f"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "n chain and Bantjies's operational control, which Bantjies had motive to conceal.\n\n## Legal Implications\n\n###"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "s. The SARS email demonstrates this was false, as Bantjies was actually directing operations through Rynette."
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "ions through Rynette.\n\n### Undisclosed Principal\n\nBantjies operated as undisclosed principal, directing finan"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "lly control the assets, and the real controllers (Bantjies and Rynette) were the ones engaging in questionabl"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "Fraud Implications\n\nIf the payments instructed by Bantjies were improper or lacked legitimate business purpos"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "# Cross-References\n\n**Related Annexures:**\n- SF1: Ketoni R18.75M debt to FFT (Bantjies conflict as George Group CFO)M) - Motive and conflic"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies\n",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": " context)\n- June 6, 2025: Daniel exposes fraud to Bantjies\n- June 10, 2025: Bantjies dismisses audit request\n"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "Daniel exposes fraud to Bantjies\n- June 10, 2025: Bantjies dismisses audit request\n\n## Notes for Legal Team\n\n"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "demonstrates:\n\n1. **Actual chain of command** was Bantjies → Rynette, not Peter → Rynette\n2. **Peter was figu"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "was figurehead** without operational control\n3. **Bantjies directed operations** while being undisclosed trus"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "ot Peter, was the actual decision-maker, and that Bantjies operated with undisclosed conflicts of interest.\n\n"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "stigation\n3. Obtain any written instructions from Bantjies to Rynette\n4. Obtain evidence of absence of instru"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies\n",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "rom Rynette confirming she took instructions from Bantjies\n8. Cross-reference payments with Bantjies's R18.68"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "# SF4: SARS Audit Email (Rynette Claiming Bantjies Instructed"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "nexure contains email correspondence related to a SARS (South African Revenue Service) audit in which Ry"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "ompany operations.\n\n## Key Evidence Required\n\n### SARS Audit Email\n\n**Primary Email:**\nComplete email fr"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "de context for Rynette's statement, including the SARS audit inquiry, questions about specific payments,"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": " requests, or challenges to the explanation.\n\n### SARS Audit Documentation\n\n**Audit Notification:**\nOffi"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "t Documentation\n\n**Audit Notification:**\nOfficial SARS audit notification letter or email specifying the"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "nd accounting treatment.\n\n**Audit Findings:**\nAny SARS audit findings, assessments, or correspondence re"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "rding the payments in question, including whether SARS accepted Rynette's explanation that Bantjies inst"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": " Peter → Rynette\n\n**Actual Structure (revealed by SARS email):**\n- Bantjies: Undisclosed trustee, accoun"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "idence\n\n### SF1: Bantjies Debt Documentation\n\nThe SARS audit email takes on additional significance when"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": " Screenshots (Rynette Using pete@regima.com)\n\nThe SARS email confirms that while Rynette used Peter's em"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "\nIf Bantjies instructed substantial payments (per SARS email), did Bantjies also instruct or approve the"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "nstrument to execute fraudulent transactions.\n\n## SARS Audit Context\n\n### Payments Under Investigation\n\n"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "it Context\n\n### Payments Under Investigation\n\nThe SARS audit context suggests the payments in question w"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "ected tax calculations.\n\n**Questionable Nature:**\nSARS had concerns about the legitimacy, business purpo"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "usiness purpose, or other red flags that prompted SARS scrutiny.\n\n### Rynette's Defense Strategy\n\nRynett"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "nto RegimA Worldwide with a 12-hour deadline. The SARS audit may have been related to these unallocated "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "as also uncovering the payments referenced in the SARS audit email, this would provide additional motive"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "eter controlled trust and company operations. The SARS email demonstrates this was false, as Bantjies wa"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "aging in questionable transactions that triggered SARS audit.\n\n### Tax Fraud Implications\n\nIf the paymen"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": " 30, 2025: Two years unallocated expenses dumped (SARS audit context)\n- June 6, 2025: Daniel exposes fra"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "eing undisclosed trustee and R18.75M (Ketoni debt to FFT) debtor\n4. **SARS investigation** suggests payments were questionab"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "avit representations about control structure\n\nThe SARS audit email is critical evidence that Peter's fou"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "f interest.\n\n**Action Items:**\n1. Obtain complete SARS audit email with full headers and thread\n2. Obtai"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "udit email with full headers and thread\n2. Obtain SARS audit documentation showing payments under invest"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "ies\n6. Prepare comparison of affidavit claims vs. SARS email revelations\n7. Obtain witness statement fro"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "South African Revenue Service",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": " contains email correspondence related to a SARS (South African Revenue Service) audit in which Rynette Farrar claimed that Bantj"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Rynette Farrar",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "annexure documents Adderory, the company owned by Rynette Farrar's son, which became a central beneficiary of the "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA  \n",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "Adderory Company Registration and Stock Supply to RegimA  \n**Relevance:** Demonstrates systematic diversion o"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "s company registration, stock supply contracts to RegimA Skin Treatments, and the registration of the compe"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": " that customers were systematically diverted from RegimA operations to the competing domain owned by Addero"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "pply agreements or contracts between Adderory and RegimA Skin Treatments, including terms, pricing, deliver"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "ments.\n\n**Purchase Orders:**\nPurchase orders from RegimA Skin Treatments to Adderory, showing products orde"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "ices:**\nComplete set of invoices from Adderory to RegimA Skin Treatments, showing:\n- Invoice dates and numb"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "owing physical delivery of stock from Adderory to RegimA Skin Treatments.\n\n**Payment Records:**\nBank statem"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "ers, and accounting records showing payments from RegimA Skin Treatments to Adderory for stock supplied.\n\n#"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": " specifications for stock supplied by Adderory to RegimA Skin Treatments, including:\n- Product codes and de"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "d content from regimaskin.co.za showing:\n- Use of RegimA branding and intellectual property\n- Product offer"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "ctual property\n- Product offerings competing with RegimA Skin Treatments\n- Customer contact information and"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "ctions (June 20, 2025):**\nEmail from Gee or other RegimA staff instructing database not to use regima.zone "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "records showing revenue that previously flowed to RegimA Skin Treatments being diverted to Adderory through"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": " (14 days later)\n- Competing domain established\n- RegimA branding and IP appropriated\n- Infrastructure for "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA\n",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "**Ongoing:** Revenue flows to Adderory instead of RegimA\n- Customers diverted to competing business\n- Value"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "rted to competing business\n- Value extracted from RegimA operations\n- Benefits flow to Rynette's family\n\n##"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "trategic Logistics (R5.4M)\n- Adderory supplies to RegimA at marked-up prices\n- Value transferred from trust"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "action of business value\n\n**IP Appropriation:**\n- RegimA logo and branding used by regimaskin.co.za\n- Intel"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "tematic diversion.\n\n**IP Transfer:**\nRynette took RegimA logo and IP information and put it in her son's na"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "ionships\n\n### Intellectual Property Theft\n\nUse of RegimA branding, logo, and IP by regimaskin.co.za without"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "pearance\n4. **IP theft** through appropriation of RegimA branding\n5. **Customer diversion** through email i"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "025)\n6. Obtain website screenshots showing use of RegimA IP\n7. Obtain financial records showing revenue div"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "ed the same type of stock that \"disappeared\" from Strategic Logistics (R5.4M), and that customers were systematically d"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "ecifications matching stock that disappeared from Strategic Logistics)\n- Quantities and unit prices\n- Total amounts and"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "nd labeling details\n- Manufacturer information\n\n**Strategic Logistics Stock Records:**\nCorresponding product specificat"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "ct specifications for stock that disappeared from Strategic Logistics, demonstrating that the stock types are identical"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "e comparison of Adderory stock specifications vs. Strategic Logistics missing stock specifications, highlighting matche"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "Supply:**\n- Same stock type that disappeared from Strategic Logistics (R5.4M)\n- Adderory supplies to RegimA at marked-u"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "# Cross-References\n\n**Related Annexures:**\n- SF3: Strategic Logistics stock adjustment - Same stock type supplied by Ad"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "uiry (7 days, 14 days)\n3. **Stock connection** to Strategic Logistics R5.4M disappearance\n4. **IP theft** through appro"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": " supply\n3. Obtain product specifications matching Strategic Logistics missing stock\n4. Obtain domain registration recor"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "ve analysis of stock specifications (Adderory vs. Strategic Logistics)\n10. Obtain witness statements from staff regardi"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "# SF5: Adderory Company Registration and Stock Supply Documentati"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "ation\n\n**Annexure Reference:** SF5  \n**Subject:** Adderory Company Registration and Stock Supply to RegimA  "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "ny\n\n## Executive Summary\n\nThis annexure documents Adderory, the company owned by Rynette Farrar's son, which"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "R1,035,000 debt).\n\nThe evidence demonstrates that Adderory supplied the same type of stock that \"disappeared"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "egimA operations to the competing domain owned by Adderory.\n\n## Key Evidence Required\n\n### Company Registrat"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": " Commission (CIPC) registration documentation for Adderory, including:\n- Company registration number\n- Date "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "ion establishing the ownership connection between Adderory and Rynette's son, including share certificates, "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": " licenses, permits, or registrations required for Adderory's operations, particularly those related to suppl"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "Any formal supply agreements or contracts between Adderory and RegimA Skin Treatments, including terms, pric"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "**\nPurchase orders from RegimA Skin Treatments to Adderory, showing products ordered, quantities, prices, an"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "ons.\n\n**Invoices:**\nComplete set of invoices from Adderory to RegimA Skin Treatments, showing:\n- Invoice dat"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "mentation showing physical delivery of stock from Adderory to RegimA Skin Treatments.\n\n**Payment Records:**\n"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "s showing payments from RegimA Skin Treatments to Adderory for stock supplied.\n\n### Stock Type Matching (Con"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "iled product specifications for stock supplied by Adderory to RegimA Skin Treatments, including:\n- Product c"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "omparative Analysis:**\nSide-by-side comparison of Adderory stock specifications vs. Strategic Logistics miss"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": ":\n- Registration date: May 29, 2025\n- Registrant: Adderory or Rynette's son\n- Registrar information\n- DNS an"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "communications\n- Use of competing domain owned by Adderory\n- Instructions sent without informing Jacqui or D"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "lowed to RegimA Skin Treatments being diverted to Adderory through the regimaskin.co.za channel.\n\n## Systema"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "29, 2025:** Domain regimaskin.co.za registered by Adderory (14 days later)\n- Competing domain established\n- "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "ersion implemented\n\n**Ongoing:** Revenue flows to Adderory instead of RegimA\n- Customers diverted to competi"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "tte's family\n\n### Value Extraction Mechanism\n\nThe Adderory scheme represents systematic value extraction thr"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "at disappeared from Strategic Logistics (R5.4M)\n- Adderory supplies to RegimA at marked-up prices\n- Value tr"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "s\n- Revenue diverted to competing domain owned by Adderory\n- Ongoing extraction of business value\n\n**IP Appr"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "ntrol Structure\n\n### Rynette's Orchestration\n\nThe Adderory scheme demonstrates Rynette's central role in orc"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "M stock adjustment that enabled stock transfer to Adderory.\n\n**Financial System Control:**\nMaintaining contr"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "st (June 10, 2025) that would have discovered the Adderory scheme.\n\n## Legal Implications\n\n### Theft and Fra"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "tic diversion of stock, customers, and revenue to Adderory constitutes theft and fraud:\n- Stock valued at R5"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "iness relationships.\n\n## Retaliation Pattern\n\nThe Adderory domain registration (May 29, 2025) fits the clear"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "cs stock adjustment - Same stock type supplied by Adderory\n- SF2: Sage screenshots - Rynette's control enabl"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "e Sections:**\n- Part II: The Network of Control - Adderory (Rynette's Son): The Beneficiary\n- Part III: Sect"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "email instructions and database manipulation\n\nThe Adderory evidence is critical to establishing that Jacqui "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "Items:**\n1. Obtain complete CIPC registration for Adderory\n2. Obtain all invoices and delivery documentation"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "btain all invoices and delivery documentation for Adderory stock supply\n3. Obtain product specifications mat"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "are comparative analysis of stock specifications (Adderory vs. Strategic Logistics)\n10. Obtain witness state"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Shopify",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "chestrating business diversion\n\n**May 22, 2025:** Shopify audit trail becomes unavailable (7 days later)\n- "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Shopify",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "nfronts Rynette (trigger event)\n**May 22, 2025:** Shopify data expunged (7 days - first retaliation)\n**May "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "CIPC",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "quired\n\n### Company Registration Documentation\n\n**CIPC Registration:**\nComplete Companies and Intellectu"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "CIPC",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "e Companies and Intellectual Property Commission (CIPC) registration documentation for Adderory, includi"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "CIPC",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "e's family.\n\n**Action Items:**\n1. Obtain complete CIPC registration for Adderory\n2. Obtain all invoices "
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Kayla Pretorius",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "# SF6: Kayla Pretorius Estate Documentation (R1,035,000 Debt)\n\n**Annexur"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Kayla Pretorius",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "nce:** SF6  \n**Subject:** R1,035,000 Debt Owed to Kayla Pretorius Estate Since February 2023  \n**Relevance:** Demon"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Kayla Pretorius",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "t owed by RegimA Skin Treatments to the estate of Kayla Pretorius since February 2023. Kayla was murdered on July 1"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Kayla Pretorius",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "ath Certificate:**\nOfficial death certificate for Kayla Pretorius showing:\n- Date of death: July 13, 2023\n- Cause o"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "is annexure documents the R1,035,000 debt owed by RegimA Skin Treatments to the estate of Kayla Pretorius s"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "ding:\n- Loan agreements or advances from Kayla to RegimA Skin Treatments\n- Invoices for services or goods p"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "ent:**\nAny written acknowledgments of the debt by RegimA Skin Treatments, including:\n- Board resolutions ac"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "t moral and legal weight:\n\n**Unjust Enrichment:**\nRegimA Skin Treatments has had use of R1,035,000 for over"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "xactly 14 days after confrontation\n- Appropriated RegimA IP and branding\n- Diverted business Jacqui built o"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "ation (36 Days Later)\n\nEmail instructions sent to RegimA database to use regimaskin.co.za addresses instead"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "ruary 14-15, 2025).\n\n**R5.4M Stock Disappeared:**\nStrategic Logistics stock \"disappeared\" and same type supplied by Add"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Villa Via",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "sappeared\" and same type supplied by Adderory.\n\n**Villa Via 86% Profit Margin:**\nTrust-owned entity extracted"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "ays Later)\n\nDomain regimaskin.co.za registered by Adderory (Rynette's son), establishing competing business "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "ics stock \"disappeared\" and same type supplied by Adderory.\n\n**Villa Via 86% Profit Margin:**\nTrust-owned en"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "ts - Rynette's control enabled non-payment\n- SF5: Adderory documentation - Domain registered 14 days after c"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Shopify",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "# May 22, 2025: First Retaliation (7 Days Later)\n\nShopify audit trail became unavailable, preventing tracki"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Kayla Pretorius",
      "source": "SF7_Court_Order_Kayla_Email_Seizure.md",
      "context": "ference:** SF7  \n**Subject:** Court Order Seizing Kayla Pretorius's Email Account  \n**Relevance:** Demonstrates int"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Kayla Pretorius",
      "source": "SF7_Court_Order_Kayla_Email_Seizure.md",
      "context": "nnexure documents a court order obtained to seize Kayla Pretorius's email account. The order is significant because"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF7_Court_Order_Kayla_Email_Seizure.md",
      "context": " their relationship to Kayla, the estate, and the RegimA entities.\n\n**Stated Grounds:**\nAnalyze stated grou"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF7_Court_Order_Kayla_Email_Seizure.md",
      "context": "niel's Audit Request Dismissed (June 10, 2025):**\nBantjies dismissed Daniel's legitimate audit request 4 days"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF7_Court_Order_Kayla_Email_Seizure.md",
      "context": "ntation - Context for email seizure motive\n- SF1: Bantjies debt documentation - Pattern of concealing evidenc"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF7_Court_Order_Kayla_Email_Seizure.md",
      "context": "qui confronts Rynette about debt\n- June 10, 2025: Bantjies dismisses audit request\n\n## Notes for Legal Team\n\n"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF7_Court_Order_Kayla_Email_Seizure.md",
      "context": "mentation - Pattern of concealing evidence\n- SF4: SARS audit email - Pattern of obstruction\n\n**Related N"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Shopify",
      "source": "SF7_Court_Order_Kayla_Email_Seizure.md",
      "context": "tents relevant to:\n- Business operations (RegimA, Shopify stores)\n- Financial transactions\n- Communications"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Rynette Farrar",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "\nThis annexure documents the employment of Linda (Rynette Farrar's sister) as bookkeeper for RegimA companies. Lin"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Rynette Farrar",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "ly network in key financial control positions:\n\n**Rynette Farrar:**\n- Controlled accounting system (Sage) using pe"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Rynette Farrar",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "e Sections:**\n- Part II: The Network of Control - Rynette Farrar: The Administrator\n- Part III: Section 5 - Two Ye"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "# SF8: Linda Employment Records (Bookkeeper)\n\n**Annexure Refer"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "eper)\n\n**Annexure Reference:** SF8  \n**Subject:** Linda Employment Records as Bookkeeper (Rynette's Siste"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "ummary\n\nThis annexure documents the employment of Linda (Rynette Farrar's sister) as bookkeeper for Regim"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "rar's sister) as bookkeeper for RegimA companies. Linda's employment is significant because, despite bein"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "questions about the competence and actual role of Linda, and whether the unallocated expenses were delibe"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "ment Contract:**\nComplete employment contract for Linda, including:\n- Start date of employment\n- Job titl"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "oof of Relationship:**\nDocumentation establishing Linda as Rynette's sister, including:\n- Birth certifica"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "s\n- Public records\n- Acknowledgment by Rynette or Linda\n\n**Conflict of Interest:**\nAnalysis of whether fa"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "e and Work Product\n\n**Work Product:**\nExamples of Linda's bookkeeping work, including:\n- Expense allocati"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "mance reviews, evaluations, or feedback regarding Linda's work:\n- Competence assessments\n- Accuracy and t"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "\n**Supervision:**\nDocumentation of who supervised Linda and how her work was reviewed:\n- Reporting struct"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "ated Expenses Analysis\n\n### The Central Question\n\nLinda was employed specifically to do the books, yet ex"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "wo years if accountant (Bantjies) and bookkeeper (Linda) were performing their duties?**\n\n### Possible Ex"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "?**\n\n### Possible Explanations\n\n**Incompetence:**\nLinda lacked competence to perform bookkeeping duties, "
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "r facilitate fraud.\n\n**Bantjies's Instructions:**\nLinda followed Bantjies's instructions not to allocate "
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": ".com) prevented proper expense allocation despite Linda's efforts.\n\n### Evidence Pointing to Deliberate S"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "nalysis\n\n### Family Network in Financial Control\n\nLinda's employment as Rynette's sister creates a family"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": " systems\n- Made all banking transactions daily\n\n**Linda (Rynette's Sister):**\n- Employed as bookkeeper\n- "
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "enses remained unallocated for two years while:\n- Linda was employed as bookkeeper\n- Bantjies was account"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "mate business purpose or proper documentation.\n\n**Linda's Role:**\nWhat was Linda's role in processing the"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "proper documentation.\n\n**Linda's Role:**\nWhat was Linda's role in processing these payments? Did she foll"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "rs of unallocated expenses\n- Failing to supervise Linda's work\n- Using unallocated expenses to conceal fr"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "es were deliberately maintained to conceal fraud, Linda's role in the scheme (whether knowing or unknowin"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "twork** in financial control positions (Rynette + Linda + Adderory)\n2. **Deliberate concealment** suggest"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "of control** enabling fraud and value extraction\n\nLinda's employment is significant not because of her in"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "s. The two years of unallocated expenses, despite Linda being employed as bookkeeper and Bantjies serving"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "*\n1. Obtain complete employment documentation for Linda\n2. Obtain proof of family relationship between Li"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "da\n2. Obtain proof of family relationship between Linda and Rynette\n3. Obtain job description and perform"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "expectations for bookkeeper\n4. Obtain examples of Linda's work product (or lack thereof)\n5. Obtain eviden"
    },
    {
      "type": "PERSON",
      "name": "Linda",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "ocated expenses\n8. Obtain witness statements from Linda about instructions received\n9. Obtain evidence of"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "Linda (Rynette Farrar's sister) as bookkeeper for RegimA companies. Linda's employment is significant becau"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "t:**\nBantjies, as professional accountant for all RegimA companies, should have immediately identified and "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "wo years of unallocated expenses were dumped into RegimA Worldwide on March 30, 2025, with a 12-hour deadli"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "RegimA ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "ng\n\nTwo years of unallocated expenses dumped into RegimA Worldwide with 12-hour deadline:\n- Daniel given in"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "ed expenses.\n\n**Concealment of Fraud:**\nThe R5.4M Strategic Logistics stock adjustment and other fraudulent transaction"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "- Supplied stock (same type that disappeared from Strategic Logistics)\n- Received diverted customers and revenue\n\n**Pat"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Strategic Logistics",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": " - Motive to conceal financial information\n- SF3: Strategic Logistics stock adjustment - Possibly concealed in unalloca"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Villa Via",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "arch 30 and June 6 to analyze expenses and expose Villa Via fraud to Bantjies:\n- Analysis revealed 86% profit"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "s\n- Review and approval procedures\n- Oversight by Bantjies (as accountant)\n\n## Two Years of Unallocated Expen"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "ked competence to perform bookkeeping duties, and Bantjies (as accountant) failed to supervise or correct the"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "penses were deliberate rather than accidental:\n\n**Bantjies as Accountant:**\nBantjies, as professional account"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": " they remained unallocated for two years suggests Bantjies permitted or orchestrated it.\n\n**Rynette's Control"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "s were subject to SARS audit, and Rynette claimed Bantjies instructed her to make payments. This suggests Ban"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "es instructed her to make payments. This suggests Bantjies was directing financial operations and would have "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "*Professional Duty:**\nAs professional accountant, Bantjies had duty to ensure accurate and timely bookkeeping"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "Trustee Duty:**\nAs trustee (even if undisclosed), Bantjies had fiduciary duty to ensure proper financial mana"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "years while:\n- Linda was employed as bookkeeper\n- Bantjies was accountant\n- Rynette controlled Sage accountin"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "tion\n- Exposure triggered immediate retaliation\n- Bantjies dismissed audit request 4 days later\n\n### June 10,"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "4 days later\n\n### June 10, 2025: Audit Dismissed\n\nBantjies dismissed Daniel's audit request:\n- Audit would ha"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "xpenses\n- Would have discovered concealed fraud\n- Bantjies protected concealment scheme by blocking audit\n\n##"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "nd in the SARS audit email (SF4), Rynette claimed Bantjies instructed her to make substantial payments. This "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": " same \"substantial payments\" that Rynette claimed Bantjies instructed?\n\n**Why Unallocated?**\nIf Bantjies inst"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "med Bantjies instructed?\n\n**Why Unallocated?**\nIf Bantjies instructed the payments, why were they left unallo"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": " system\n- SF4: SARS audit email - Rynette claimed Bantjies instructed payments\n- SF1: Bantjies debt documenta"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "nette claimed Bantjies instructed payments\n- SF1: Bantjies debt documentation - Motive to conceal financial i"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies\n",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": " deadline\n- June 6, 2025: Daniel exposes fraud to Bantjies\n- June 10, 2025: Bantjies dismisses audit request\n"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "Daniel exposes fraud to Bantjies\n- June 10, 2025: Bantjies dismisses audit request\n\n## Notes for Legal Team\n\n"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Bantjies ",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "s, despite Linda being employed as bookkeeper and Bantjies serving as accountant, suggests systematic conceal"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": " allocation\n- Worked under Rynette's direction\n\n**Adderory (Rynette's Son):**\n- Registered competing domain "
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "Adderory",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "in financial control positions (Rynette + Linda + Adderory)\n2. **Deliberate concealment** suggested by two y"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "dump to create confusion and prevent analysis.\n\n**SARS Audit Context:**\nThe unallocated expenses were su"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "ntext:**\nThe unallocated expenses were subject to SARS audit, and Rynette claimed Bantjies instructed he"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "ant\n- Rynette controlled Sage accounting system\n- SARS audit was pending or ongoing\n\n### March 30, 2025:"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "alment scheme by blocking audit\n\n## Connection to SARS Audit (SF4)\n\nThe unallocated expenses were subjec"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "t (SF4)\n\nThe unallocated expenses were subject to SARS audit, and in the SARS audit email (SF4), Rynette"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "d expenses were subject to SARS audit, and in the SARS audit email (SF4), Rynette claimed Bantjies instr"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "r Rynette's instructions not to allocate them?\n\n**SARS Investigation:**\nWhat did SARS conclude about the"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": " allocate them?\n\n**SARS Investigation:**\nWhat did SARS conclude about the unallocated expenses? Were the"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "s - Rynette's control of accounting system\n- SF4: SARS audit email - Rynette claimed Bantjies instructed"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": "ailure to supervise or correct\n4. **Connection to SARS audit** and Bantjies's payment instructions\n5. **"
    },
    {
      "type": "ORG",
      "name": "SARS",
      "source": "SF8_Linda_Employment_Records.md",
      "context": " have been allocated vs. when they were\n7. Obtain SARS audit documentation regarding unallocated expense"
    }
  ],
  "relations_found": [
    {
      "from_entity": "685M",
      "to_entity": "Faucitt Family Trust",
      "relation_type": "DEBT",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "685M Debt to Faucitt Family Trust"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "000",
      "to_entity": "by Bantjies to the Faucitt Family Trust",
      "relation_type": "DEBT",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "000 owed by Bantjies to the Faucitt Family Trust"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "Duty to collect debts",
      "to_entity": "to the trust",
      "relation_type": "DEBT",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "Duty to collect debts owed to the trust"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "s own substantial",
      "to_entity": "the trust",
      "relation_type": "DEBT",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "s own substantial debt to the trust"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "Undisclosed",
      "to_entity": "the Faucitt Family Trust\n2",
      "relation_type": "FIDUCIARY",
      "source": "SF1_Ketoni_Debt_FFT_Documentation.md",
      "context": "Undisclosed trustee of the Faucitt Family Trust\n2"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "Executive Summary\n\nThis annexure contains screenshots and system logs demonstrating that Rynette Farrar",
      "to_entity": "the Sage accounting system using Peter",
      "relation_type": "CONTROL",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "Executive Summary\n\nThis annexure contains screenshots and system logs demonstrating that Rynette Farrar controlled the Sage accounting system using Peter"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "and other settings",
      "to_entity": "by Rynette",
      "relation_type": "CONTROL",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "and other settings controlled by Rynette"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "Rynette",
      "to_entity": "the timing and execution",
      "relation_type": "CONTROL",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "Rynette controlled the timing and execution"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "Rynette",
      "to_entity": "accounting records showing debt status",
      "relation_type": "CONTROL",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "Rynette controlled accounting records showing debt status"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "System access",
      "to_entity": "by Rynette",
      "relation_type": "CONTROL",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "System access controlled by Rynette"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "Rynette",
      "to_entity": "the accounting records Daniel analyzed",
      "relation_type": "CONTROL",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "Rynette controlled the accounting records Daniel analyzed"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "Cancellations processed through banking systems",
      "to_entity": "by Rynette",
      "relation_type": "CONTROL",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "Cancellations processed through banking systems controlled by Rynette"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "Establishes who actually",
      "to_entity": "operations",
      "relation_type": "CONTROL",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "Establishes who actually controlled operations"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "s founding affidavit contains material misrepresentations about who actually",
      "to_entity": "the trust and company operations",
      "relation_type": "CONTROL",
      "source": "SF2_Sage_Screenshots_Rynette_Control.md",
      "context": "s founding affidavit contains material misrepresentations about who actually controlled the trust and company operations"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "RegimA Skin Treatments",
      "to_entity": "R1",
      "relation_type": "DEBT",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "RegimA Skin Treatments owes R1"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "occurred while Bantjies was accountant and Rynette",
      "to_entity": "the accounting system",
      "relation_type": "CONTROL",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "occurred while Bantjies was accountant and Rynette controlled the accounting system"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "Value is",
      "to_entity": "Rynette",
      "relation_type": "TRANSFER",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "Value is transferred from trust-controlled entities to Rynette"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "Transfer Pricing Fraud\n\nIf stock was",
      "to_entity": "extract value from trust",
      "relation_type": "TRANSFER",
      "source": "SF3_Strategic_Logistics_Stock_Adjustment.md",
      "context": "Transfer Pricing Fraud\n\nIf stock was transferred from Strategic Logistics to Adderory and then sold to RegimA at marked-up prices, this constitutes transfer pricing fraud designed to extract value from trust"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "685M",
      "to_entity": "identify any debt reduction",
      "relation_type": "DEBT",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "685M debt to identify any debt reduction"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "This directly contradicts the representation that Peter",
      "to_entity": "trust and company operations",
      "relation_type": "CONTROL",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "This directly contradicts the representation that Peter controlled trust and company operations"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "s founding affidavit implies that Peter",
      "to_entity": "trust and company operations",
      "relation_type": "CONTROL",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "s founding affidavit implies that Peter controlled trust and company operations"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "s founding affidavit contains material misrepresentations about who actually",
      "to_entity": "trust and company operations",
      "relation_type": "CONTROL",
      "source": "SF4_SARS_Audit_Email.md",
      "context": "s founding affidavit contains material misrepresentations about who actually controlled trust and company operations"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "com or other",
      "to_entity": "addresses",
      "relation_type": "CONTROL",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "com or other controlled addresses"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "Value",
      "to_entity": "Rynette",
      "relation_type": "TRANSFER",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "Value transferred from trust-controlled entities to Rynette"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "Rynette",
      "to_entity": "the new domain",
      "relation_type": "TRANSFER",
      "source": "SF5_Adderory_Company_Registration_Stock_Supply.md",
      "context": "Rynette sent emails (using pete@regima.com or other controlled addresses) instructing staff to divert customers to the new domain"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "000 Debt",
      "to_entity": "to Kayla Pretorius Estate Since February 2023",
      "relation_type": "DEBT",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "000 Debt Owed to Kayla Pretorius Estate Since February 2023"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "000 debt",
      "to_entity": "by RegimA Skin Treatments to the estate of Kayla Pretorius since February 2023",
      "relation_type": "DEBT",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "000 debt owed by RegimA Skin Treatments to the estate of Kayla Pretorius since February 2023"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "000 debt",
      "to_entity": "to Kayla",
      "relation_type": "DEBT",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "000 debt owed to Kayla"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "Jacqui investigated unpaid",
      "to_entity": "Kayla",
      "relation_type": "DEBT",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "Jacqui investigated unpaid debt to Kayla"
    },
    {
      "from_entity": "Connection to Broader Fraud Pattern\n\nThe unpaid",
      "to_entity": "Kayla",
      "relation_type": "DEBT",
      "source": "SF6_Kayla_Pretorius_Estate_Documentation.md",
      "context": "Connection to Broader Fraud Pattern\n\nThe unpaid debt to Kayla"
    },
    {
